JODIE KWOK



https://www.linkedin.com/in/kwyjodiecs



jodiekwy[at]gmail.com



https://jodiekwy.github.io/ jo-label

Detail-oriented and task-driven software developer with a background in computer science and 4+ years experiences. Development experience with different technologies that are widely used in the industry. Refactored services into automate processed and REST based microservices.

SKILLS

Programming Languages: Java, Python, MySQL, PostgreSQL, DynamonDB, HTML, XML, CSS, JavaScript, Angular

Others: PyCharm, IntelliJ IDEA, Spring Framework, Django Framework, Kubernetes, Spinnaker, Jenkins, AWS

LEADERSHIP EXPERIENCES

Lead Sprint Planner, Fidelity Investment, February 2018-April 2018

- Led a discussion among the development team to assign stories and clarify acceptance criteria
- Prepared bi-weekly demo and a short status report to the business team and follow up on any user's feedback

WORK EXPERIENCES

Senior Software Developer, Hulu March 2020-present

Los Angeles, CA

- Backend Software Developer on the Ad Platform team; build microservices to support the Hulu's self-service Advertising Platform—Hulu Ad Manager
- Focus on the invoicing and payment system and integrate with multiple internal and external parties
- Engage in the system design for the brand-new Disney Ad Platform with a serverless microservices architecture, including order and targeting systems

Java Developer (Consultant), JPMorgan Chase (TEKsystems) May 2019-Feb 2020 Newport, NJ

- Developed REST based microservices to expose different types of banking risk assessment functionalities to Chase customers in a high-volume, high-availability application
- Participated in end-to-end development lifecycle activities of the application, including design, coding, testing and deployment
- Coordinated and collaborated with technical partners for joint application development/testing efforts

Associate Software Engineer, Fidelity Investment Newport, NJ January 2018-April 2019

- Backend and middle-tier developer on the Fully Paid Lending Program team, a fault-tolerant platform for securities lending market under Fidelity Prime Services
- Managed the messaging system (MQ) for a secure data transmission between different system internally

IT Administrator, CipherTechs, September 2016-November 2017

New York, NY

- Maintained a smooth operation of the internal network, set up domain policies and deployed software updates to users
- Identified computer problems and advised on the solution through research

EDUCATION

Stony Brook University Stony Brook, NY Bachelor of Science, Computer Science, December 2016

- Related Coursework: Software Engineering, Database System, Web-based Software Development
- Dean's List: Spring 2015 & Fall 2014 & Spring2014 & Fall2013